<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lim Blog</title>
    <link>https://lim-blog.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lim Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://lim-blog.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>5 Biggest Insights From 50 Self Help Books</title>
      <link>https://lim-blog.netlify.app/posts/5-biggest-insights-from-50-self-help-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lim-blog.netlify.app/posts/5-biggest-insights-from-50-self-help-books/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1519791883288-dc8bd696e667?crop=entropy&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;fit=max&amp;amp;fm=jpg&amp;amp;ixid=M3wzNjAwOTd8MHwxfHNlYXJjaHwyN3x8cmVhZGluZ3xlbnwwfDB8fHwxNzMzNzM5NzY4fDA&amp;amp;ixlib=rb-4.0.3&amp;amp;q=80&amp;amp;w=1080&#34; alt=&#34;Now I can read in the dark.&#34;&gt;&#xA;I still remember the first ever self help book I&amp;rsquo;ve read - &amp;ldquo;Borrowing Brilliance&amp;rdquo; by David Kord Murray. The book was about how creative ideas are generated and how you can train yourself to be creative. That book had greatly helped me in learning the underlying process of thinking outside the box, but that was just the gist of it. What was perhaps the most valuable thing the book had given to me was the realization that books can alter your perspective about life itself. I was stunned to realize that reading a book is like entering a whole unique world, exploring new ideas and perspectives, and exiting as a changed, different person. From that point on, I was super interested in reading self help books and I&amp;rsquo;ve devoted myself into reading more. Until today, I&amp;rsquo;ve read over 50 self help books, and needless to say that I benefitted from each and every one of them. Today, I would like to share with you 5 of the biggest insights I&amp;rsquo;ve got from the 50 books I&amp;rsquo;ve read. These 5 insights are lifechanging to me, and they had greatly influenced how I viewed the world of today. Without further ado, here we go!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
